{
    "subject": "resource/Matti_Manushulu",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Telugu-language_films",
    "human_readable": "Matti Manushulu is about Telugu-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9662408232688904,
            "question": "Are there any famous Telugu-language films that Matti Manushulu might discuss?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9625015258789062,
            "question": "What kind of information would you expect to find about Telugu-language films from Matti Manushulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8914913535118103,
            "question": "What is Matti Manushulu about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803588151931763,
            "question": "How does Matti Manushulu contribute to our understanding of Telugu cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8030951023101807,
            "question": "What type of films does Matti Manushulu focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7843522429466248,
            "question": "Is Matti Manushulu related to a specific film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7274340391159058,
            "question": "What language are Telugu-language films made in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5621563792228699,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Matti Manushulu's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5368166565895081,
            "question": "What are some common themes or genres found in Telugu-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5215513706207275,
            "question": "Who or what is likely the target audience for Matti Manushulu's content?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matti Manushulu is about Telugu-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4743_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes or genres found in Telugu-language films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4743_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Matti Manushulu's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4743_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language are Telugu-language films made in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4743_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4743_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Matti Manushulu is about Telugu-language films.\" Specifically, they mention it as a 1990 Indian Telugu-language drama film directed by B. Narsing Rao and produced in India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}